Haemin Ryu | Curriculum Vitae

My vision is to improve human mobility experiences with emerging technology and by analyzing data to make more people access the novel world without barriers, regardless of impairments and age.

My interests rest at the intersection of Human-Computer Interaction (HCI), Universal Design, Extended Reality, and Accessibility.

haeminryu.com 📧 design.haemin.ryu@gmail.com

Education

Mar. 2014-Feb. 2020

Dual Degree Program Scholar

Graduated Dec.2019

B. S. in Computer Science

Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN, USA

Honors: PFW Top 50 (Annually recognizes 50 students for outstanding work and extracurricular achievements)

Graduated Feb.2020

B. E. in Computer Science

Seoul Women's University, Seoul, South Korea

Honors: Merit-based Scholar with Highest Distinction (Full-ride tuition granted for two semesters)

Summa Cum Laude (3 of 71 students, in the top 1-5% of the Computer Science Major class)

Professional Experience

Jan. 2020-Present

Software Developer

Cirrus ABS Corporation (MarketSnare)

- Delivered a local marketing web platform 'MarketSnare' that meets multi-location business needs with centralized management, localization, and customization for various regions.
- Developed web solutions with the MarketSnare software platforms using the Microsoft ASP.NET framework, C#, XML, XSLT, JSON, HTML/CSS/JS, API integrations, Database management, and Web Server Technologies.

Research Experience

ongoing

[2] Menu interfaces to Avoid Disembodiment Situations in Virtual Reality

Advisor: Dr. Beomjin Kim

 Analyze different menu styles to investigate the way to help improve menu interface design in Virtual Reality focused on the disembodiment issue.

2020 [1] Improvement to Pix2Code using Fast.ai: Automatic Generation of GUI with a Model Classification

Advisor: Dr. Venkata Inukollu

- Demonstrated that automated deep learning model classification using Fast.ai can improve the accuracy and speed of the Pix2Code GUI Generation.

Selected Projects

Oct. 2021

[2] PLUR: Online Platform for Physical Education Community for Individuals with Disabilities

#Accessibility #Sports #Community

- Created a web app that uses local resources and crowdsourcing to make sports programs and facilities more accessible to individuals with disabilities.
- Developed scenarios for connecting differently abled children and young adults with verified local coaches, trainers, sports associations, and clubs to begin their journey in sports.

Aug. 2019-Apr. 2020

[1] Indoor Navigation: Improved Accessibility for People with Disabilities

#Accessibility #DataVisualization #Navigation #Hospital

- Leveraged hospital navigation data from beacon technology focused on the patient experience to provide a more accessible hospital visit experience for patients with disabilities.
- Designed a data analytics web application to discover heavy/light usage facilities and routes at the hospital and improved mobile application navigation to assist patients.
- Built a web interface that visualizes interactive data analytics and displays employee administration management systems using Angular 7, TypeScript, and HTML/CSS/JS.

	Twards & Honors			
	Academic Conferences			
Oct. 2022	Travel Award, ACM UIST Conference, USD 1,338			
Feb. 2020	Student Mentoring Workshop, IEEE/ACM ICSE Conference, USD 500			
Oct. 2019	Purdue Student Travel Fund Grant for IEEE/ACM ASE Conference, Purdue Global, USD 1,164.83			
4 2000	Scholastic Achievements			
Apr. 2020	Student Research and Creative Endeavor Symposium - Poster, Purdue FW Research & Innovation			
Apr. 2019	Purdue Fort Wayne Top 50 Award, Purdue FW Top 50 Committee			
2018, 2019	Dean's List & Semester Honors List, Purdue FW Engineering, Technology, and Computer Science			
2018, 2019	Dual Degree Program Scholarship, SWU Division of International Affairs, 2-year Full-ride tuition			
2014, 2015	Merit-based Scholarship, SWU College of Informatics & Media, 2-semester Full-ride tuition			
	Collaborative Project Team Achievements			
Oct. 2021	Hack for Humanity - Top 7 Finalist of 59 worldwide competitors, Arizona State University			
Feb. 2021				
May. 2019	Capstone Design Project Excellence Award - 2 nd Place, Purdue FW Dept. of Computer Science			
Nov. 2015	Creative Idea Competition Award - 1st Place, SWU Creative Center, KRW 300,000 (USD 279)			
Jul. 2015	LIKELION Ideathon - Top 10 out of 110 projects with over 500 college students in Korea, LIKELION			
	Presentations			
Apr. 8th, 2022	Ryu, H. (2022). UX Design for Web Developers. University of Illinois Web Conference, University of Illinois,			
Αρι. στι, 2022	Champaign, IL (Virtual). April 6-8, 2022.			
Oct. 2019	Ryu, H. (2019). Journey to Conference on Automated Software Engineering. Guest Lecture for			
	CS 36000 Software Engineering, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. October 2019.			
	Panels			
Dec. 7th, 2022	Professional Panel, CS 46700 Project Management, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. Department of Computer Science			
Nov. 28th, 2022				
Apr. 15th, 2022	Q & A with Alumni Panel, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. College of Engineering, Technology & Computer Science			
Apr. 12th, 2021	ETCS Internship Panel, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. College of Engineering, Technology & Computer Science			
Nov. 20th, 2019	"A Day in their Shoes" Simulation with Panel Discussion, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. Office of			
	International Education			
	Teaching Experience			
	Teaching Assistant			
Fall 2018–Fall 2019	CS 36000 Software Engineering			
Summer 2010	Venkata Inukollu, Ph.D. Assistant Professor; Department of Computer Science; Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN			
Summer 2019	CS 16000 Intro to Computer Science I (Java) David Liu, Ph.D. Associate Professor; Department of Computer Science; Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN			
	Tutoring			
Fall 2018–Spring 2019	Core Academic Skills Assessment (CASA), Analytic Geometry and Calculus I & II			
M 2016 N 2016				

Mar. 2016–Nov. 2016 Play with Software - Programming education for elementary school students, NAVER Connect Fdn.

Awards & Honors

Volunteering & Extra Curricular

Academic	Services	- Student	Volunteer

Oct. 2022, 2021, 2020 ACM UIST Conference

May. 2021 ACM CHI Conference

Jul. 2020 IEEE/ACM ICSE Conference

UX/UI Design

Aug. 2021–Mar. 2022 Seed Fund Initiative Project, United Nations SDSN Global Youth

Aug. 2021–Oct. 2021 Lead Like a Girl Challenge Project for Young Women Leaders, Go Laadli

Leadership

Feb. 2020 Site Organizer, Global Game Jam Fort Wayne, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. Department of Computer Science

2018–2019 Association for Computing Machinery, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. Department of Computer Science

2018–2019 Club Seoul Event Coordinator, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. International Student Organization

Apr. 2018, Apr. 2019 The BIG Event: Student-led service project, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN.

Summer 2018 New Student Orientation Program Assistant, Purdue University, Fort Wayne, IN. Department of Computer

Science

Spring 2014–Fall 2014 Student Council, Seoul Women's University, Seoul, South Korea. Department of Computer Science

Sep, 2014 – Dec. 2014 Young Lab Marketing, Samsung Card, Seoul, South Korea.

Other Services

Nov. 2017 Volunteer, Coal Briquettes for Neighbors in Korea

Jun. 2017 Volunteer, Dongan Intellectual and Developmental Disabilities Retreat

Jul. 2017–Aug. 2017 'I'm your PEN' Translator, Good Neighbors

Jun, 2014- Oct. 2014 Seismic Outreach Volunteer, Into Dreams and People Youth Overseas Volunteer Group, the Ministry of Gender

Equality and Family of Korea, Korea Youth Work Agency, and Korea Rotary Youth Association